## ATHARV MISHRA

# Mobile App Developer (Android and Flutter)

+91-8755328239

atharvmishra77@gmail.com

My links:- <u>https://atharv-portfolio-ashy.vercel.app</u>

Noida

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Rising star in WIPRO Q4-2022
- Was part of NIT Rourkela Hacksagon 2023
- Among top Performers in 2023

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Technology** 

GL Bajaj Group Of Institutions, Mathura

2017 - 2021

#### **SKILLS**

- Languages: Kotlin, Java, Dart
- Development Tools: Android Studio, VS Code
- Frameworks & Libraries: Android Jetpack, Retrofit, Room, Dagger Hilt, Coroutines, Flutter, Provider, Riverpod, BLoC.
- · Version Control: Git
- UI/UX Design: Material Design principles, responsive layouts, Flutter UI Components (Widgets, CustomPainter, Animations).
- CI/CD Pipeline: Jenkins.
- Architectures MVC & MVVM, Clean Architecture (Flutter)
- AI/ML NLP, ANN, Deep Learning

#### **LANGUAGES**

- · Hindi
- · English

### **OTHER PROJECTS**

#### Hello NITR (NIT Rourkela) Flutter App

 Built a Flutter-based app for NIT Rourkela that bridges the communication gap between faculty and students.

Link: <u>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?</u> id=com.nitrkl.hellonitr&pcampaignid=web\_share

#### **NoNames Social Media**

- Integrated AWS facial recognition for secure user verification.
- Developed VoIP-based low-latency internet calling.
- Built a *chat system* with multimedia, encryption, and delivery indicators.

Link: <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?</a>
<a href="mailto:id=com.nonamessocialmedia&pcampaignid=web-share">id=com.nonamessocialmedia&pcampaignid=web-share</a>

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a passionate Android developer with over 3 years of experience in creating mobile applications that enhance the user experience. My expertise lies in developing feature-rich *Android* and *cross-platform* Mobile apps using *Kotlin, Java, Jetpack-compose* and *Flutter* with a strong focus on best practices and user-centric design.

My work: https://atharv-portfolio-ashy.vercel.app/

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

QueueBuster (NOIDA)

Aug 2024 - Oct 2024

#### **Mobile App Developer**

**Self-Service Kiosk App** 

• Led the development of a *Flutter-based* self-service kiosk app for renowned restaurant chains like *Chili's* and *McDonald's*, enhancing order efficiency and customer experience.

#### **IoT-Enabled Check-In System**

Engineered a Android Based smart check-in system with *IoT-controlled* flap barriers for *Wonderla*, a leading amusement park chain, ensuring seamless and secure guest entry.

## Unnati AgriTech (NOIDA)

Feb 2023- August 2024

**Android App Developer** 

- Developed entire *Ora Finance App* with *MVVM*, implmented *E-Mandate* & *KYC*.
- Enhanced *U-store App* (100K+ downloads) by migrating *Java to Kotlin*.
- Optimized API calls with *Retrofit* and replaced *SQLite* with *RoomDB*.
- Integrated payment gateways and third-party SDKs.

ORA FINANCE: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.app.orafinancecustomer
U-STORE: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.unnatiagro.agripos&pcampaignid=web\_share

# • WIPRO Technologies (Gurugram) Aug 2021 - Feb 2023

**SDET (Software Development Engineer in Test)** 

- Designed, developed, and maintained automated test scripts using Java Selenium framework.
- Worked on agile methodology with the help of tools like *Jira and Confluenece*.
- Integrated automated tests with the CI/CD pipeline to ensure continuous testing.
- Ensured that the automation coverage includes functional, regression, performance, and load testing.

# ■ LogicLadder Technologies (Gurugram) March 2021 - July 2021 Android App Developer (*Intern*)

- Contributed to developing an Android app for a sustainability management technology company.
- Worked on Bluetooth which collects the data from difference Sensors.
- · Built user interfaces, integrated APIs.
- Worked under the guidance of senior developers to enhance app functionality.